Guide to the Hotel Employees and Restaurant Employees International Union, Local 6 Records WAG.148
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series II: General Files
  - Dues, 1960s; 1980 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Dues: Delinquent, 1981-1983 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Dues: Referendum, 1973-1980 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Election: Administrative Slate, 1951 (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Election: Convention Candidate Statements, District 1, 1954 (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - Election: Convention Candidate Statements, District 2, 1954 (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - Election: Convention Candidate Statements, District 4, 1954 (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - Election: Convention Candidate Statements, District 6 (Banquet), 1954 (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - Election: Convention Candidate Statements, District 7 (Clubs), 1954 (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - Election: Expenses, 1951 (Box 9, Folder 19)
  - Election Case: U.S. Department of Labor vs. Local 6, 1965-1969 (Box 9, Folder 20)
  - Election Case: U.S. Department of Labor vs. Local 6, Correspondence, 1965-1969 (Box 9, Folder 21)
  - Election and Objections Committee, 1968 (Box 9, Folder 22)
  - Elections, undated (Box 9, Folder 23)
  - Elections, 1950-1959 (Box 9, Folder 24)
  - Elections, 1960-1969 (Box 9, Folder 25)
  - Elections, 1971-1977 (Box 9, Folder 26)
  - Elections: Membership Party, undated (Box 9, Folder 27)
  - Equal Employment Opportunity Commission, 1982 (Box 9, Folder 28)
  - Essay Contest, 1964 (Box 9, Folder 29)
  - Executive Board: General, 1986-1988 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Executive Board: List, 1962-1982 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Executive Board and Assembly: Meeting Notices, 1980-1982 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Expense Account Laws, 1977 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Farah Strike, 1972-1974 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Ferrara, Joseph, undated (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Finances, 1970-1975 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Finances, 1976-1987 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Food and Beverage Trades Department, AFL-CIO, 1981-1982 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Food Industry Survey, 1973 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Garob, Inc., 1944-1952 (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Garob, Inc.: Ledgers, 1946-1952 (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - General Officers Meeting, 1981-1983 (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - Greater New York Fund, 1960-1963 (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - Greenbaum, Joseph: Pension Claim, 1959-1977 (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - Grievance Board, 1986 (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - Grievances, 1964 (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - Grievances, 1965 (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - Grievances, 1966 (Box 10, Folder 19)
  - Grievances, 1967 (Box 10, Folder 20)
  - Grievances, 1981-1982 (Box 10, Folder 21)
  - Grievances: Members' Complaints, 1981-1982 (Box 10, Folder 22)
  - Health and Safety, 1952 (Box 10, Folder 23)
  - Haitian Refugees, 1974-1980 (Box 10, Folder 24)
  - Hispanic Members, undated; 1979 (Box 10, Folder 25)
  - History: General, undated; 1985 (Box 10, Folder 26)
  - Hoh, Jospeh: Correspondence, 1943-1950 (Box 10, Folder 27)
  - Hoh, Jospeh: Correspondence, 1951 (Box 10, Folder 28)
  - Hoh, Jospeh: Misc. Invoices, 1946-1953 (Box 10, Folder 29)
  - Hoh, Jospeh: Personal, 1944-1952 (Box 10, Folder 30)
  - Horn and Hardart, 1965 (Box 10, Folder 31)
  - Horn and Hardart: Strike, 1937 (Box 10, Folder 32)
  - Hotel Employees and Restaurant Employees International Union (HERE): Hotel Guide, 1977 (Box 10, Folder 33)
  - HERE: Pension, undated (Box 10, Folder 34)
  - HERE: Pension and Welfare Funds, 1978-1979 (Box 10, Folder 35)
  - Hotel and Club Voice: Correspondence, 1958-1974 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Hotel Division: Leaflets, 1930s-1940s (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Hotel Industry: Figures Summarized, 1980 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Hotel Industry: Race Survey, 1964 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Hotels: Delinquency List, 1987 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Hotels: Helmsley Palace, undated; 1986 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Hotels: Proposed Legislation, 1955 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Hotels: Puerto Rico, 1985; 1987 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Hotels: U.S. Department of Labor Report, [1953] (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Hotels: Loew's/Tisch, 1960s (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Hotels: Zeckendorf Corp., 1959 (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Howard Johnson Co., 1981 (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Industry Training Program, 1982 (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - Industry Training Program: List of Graduates, 1979 (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - Industry Training Program: Questionnaire, I, undated (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - Industry Training Program: Questionnaire, II, undated (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - Inhilco, Inc., 1982 (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - In-Plant Shops: Dues Letters, 1982 (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - Installation of Officers, 1962 (Box 11, Folder 19)
  - Insurance Fund, undated (Box 11, Folder 20)
  - Insurance Fund, 1950-1960 (Box 11, Folder 21)
  - Insurance Fund, 1961-1963 (Box 11, Folder 22)
  - Insurance Fund, 1977-1985 (Box 11, Folder 23)
  - Insurance Fund, 1989 (Box 11, Folder 24)
  - Insurance Fund: Blue Cross, Blue Shield, 1966 (Box 11, Folder 25)
  - Insurance Fund: Correspondence, 1974-1975 (Box 11, Folder 26)
  - International Union of Food and Allied Workers, 1975-1981 (Box 11, Folder 27)
  - Joyce Contracting, 1980-1981 (Box 11, Folder 28)
  - Kamaras, Vangel, undated (Box 11, Folder 29)
  - Koch, Edward, 1979-1983 (Box 11, Folder 30)
  - Labor Day Parades, 1981-1983 (Box 11, Folder 31)
  - LeBron, Lucy, 1974-1983 (Box 11, Folder 32)
  - LeBron, Lucy: Anonymous Letters, 1982 (Box 11, Folder 33)
  - LeBron, Lucy: Discrimination Complaints, 1981-1982 (Box 11, Folder 34)
  - LeBron, Lucy: Harassment Charges, 1987 (Box 11, Folder 35)
  - Legislative, 1955; 1977 (Box 11, Folder 36)
  - Local 1: Welfare and Pension Fund, 1969-1973 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Local 5, Hawaii, 1973-1974 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Local 7: Newsletter, 1947 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Local 15: Steinberg Case, 1962 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Local 16: Election, 1938 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Local 16: Funds, Death Benefits and Attendance Letter, 1946-1960 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Local 22, 1977 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Local 26, Boston, 1982 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Local 32A: Newsletter, 1939 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Local 42: Election, 1938 (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Local 43, Upholsterers, 1943-1959 (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Local 56, 1959 (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Local 69, Bartenders: Agreements, 1979 (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - Local 69: Arbitration, Bollano, Arlene and Torsiello, Josephine (Harry M. Stevens, Inc./Meadowlands), 1977-1978 (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - Local 69: Arbitration, Caserta, Eugene et al. vs. Winged Foot Golf Club (I), 1977-1978 (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - Local 69: Arbitration, Caserta, Eugene et al. vs. Winged Foot Golf Club (II), 1977-1978 (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - Local 69: Arbitration, Castillo, Guillermo (Beef Steak Charlie), 1979 (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - Local 69: Arbitration, David, Raymonde (Restaurant Associates/The Brasserie), 1979 (Box 12, Folder 18)
  - Local 69: Arbitration, Hinton, R. (Ogden Food Service Corp.), 1978 (Box 12, Folder 19)
  - Local 69: Arbitration, IPL Food, Inc. d/b/a Fair and Square Restaurant, 1949 (Box 12, Folder 20)
  - Local 69: Arbitration, Mulligan, Daniel (Lake Isle Country Club), 1978-1979 (Box 12, Folder 21)
  - Local 69: Arbitration, Nieves, John (Apowamis Country Club), 1979 (Box 12, Folder 22)
  - Local 69: Arbitration, Simpson, Louvenia (ARA Service, Inc.), 1979 (Box 12, Folder 23)
  - Local 69: Arbitration, Snow, Richard (Gallaghers Steak House), 1979 (Box 12, Folder 24)
  - Local 69: Arbitration, Zaloumis, Derecos; Spano (Daly's Dandelion), 1978 (Box 12, Folder 25)
  - Local 69: Finances, 1981-1982 (Box 12, Folder 26)
  - Local 69: Grievance, Caserta, Eugene, 1977 (Box 12, Folder 27)
  - Local 69: Grievance, Caserta, Eugene, 1978 (Box 12, Folder 28)
  - Local 69: Grievance, Federation of Employees Local 1027 vs. Dobbs Airline Service, 1978 (Box 12, Folder 29)
  - Local 69: Grievance, Hydock, Joseph (St. Andrew's Golf Club), 1979 (Box 12, Folder 30)
  - Local 69: Grievance, Raegner, Louis C. III (Leewood Golf Club), 1978 (Box 12, Folder 31)
  - Local 69: Grievance, Rosato, Lorraine (Harding Williams Dixie Corp./Schraffts Saga), 1978 (Box 12, Folder 32)
  - Local 69: Grievance, Sorrento, Rose; Sjusen, Josephine; Hoffman, Catherine; Leghorn, Ruth (Service Systems Corp.), 1974-1978 (Box 12, Folder 33)
  - Local 69: Grievance, Zaloumis, Derecos, Spano (Daly's Dandelion) (I), 1976-1978 (Box 12, Folder 34)
  - Local 69: Grievance, Zaloumis, Derecos, Spano (Daly's Dandelion) (II), 1976-1978 (Box 12, Folder 35)
  - Local 69: Harry M. Stevens, Inc., 1976-1980 (Box 12, Folder 36)
  - Local 69: Knotty Pine Lanes, 1974-1980 (Box 12, Folder 37)
  - Local 69: Petition, Teamsters (Plainview Enterprises Corp.), 1978 (Box 12, Folder 38)
  - Local 69: Petition, United Brotherhood of Industrial Workers Local 424 (Lockman Food Service), 1978 (Box 12, Folder 39)
  - Local 89, 1979-1980 (Box 12, Folder 40)
  - Local 89: Agreement, 1962 (Box 12, Folder 41)
  - Local 94, 1946 (Box 12, Folder 42)
  - Local 100, 1983 (Box 12, Folder 43)
  - Local 100B, Telephone Operators, 1950-1953 (Box 12, Folder 44)
  - Local 144, Hotel Front Service Employees, undated (Box 12, Folder 45)
  - Local 144, 1940-1979 (Box 12, Folder 46)
  - Local 144: GGG Operating Corp. vs. Local 144, 1966 (Box 12, Folder 47)
  - Local 144: Opposition to Contract Ratification, Peter Ottley (I), 1978 (Box 12, Folder 48)
  - Local 144: Opposition to Contract Ratification, Peter Ottley (II), 1978 (Box 12, Folder 49)
  - Local 144: Pension Fund, undated (Box 12, Folder 50)
  - Local 178, Bartenders, 1980 (Box 12, Folder 51)
  - Local 302: Women's Committee, 1963 (Box 12, Folder 52)
  - Local 610, Puerto Rico, 1976-1982 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Local 610: Clippings, 1978 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Local 610: Clippings Scrapbook, undated (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Local 610: Clippings Scrapbook, 1972-1974 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Local 610: Clippings Scrapbook, 1976 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Local 610: Clippings Scrapbook, 1976 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Local 610: Clippings Scrapbook, 1977 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Local 1422, 1940 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Local Joint Executive Board, 1970-1971 (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Local Joint Executive Board, 1972-1978 (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Madison Square Garden Meeting, 1972 (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - March on Washington: Anti-War, 1969 (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - Master Agreements, 1976-1981 (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - Maxon Company, 1987 (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - Meany Award, 1987 (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - Medical Advisory Committee, 1968-1968 (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - Members' Complaints, undated; 1958-1983 (Box 13, Folder 17)
  - Membership: Applications, Traveling Cards, etc., 1972-1975 (Box 13, Folder 18)
  - Membership Meetings: Leaflets, 1972-1975 (Box 13, Folder 19)
  - Membership Party, undated (Box 13, Folder 20)
  - "Membership Voice": Newsletter, undated; 1963-1964 (Box 13, Folder 21)
  - Merger, 1980 (Box 13, Folder 22)
  - Merger: Correspondence, 1980 (Box 13, Folder 23)
  - Miami, 1975-1977 (Box 13, Folder 24)
  - Minimum Wage, 1957-1960 (Box 13, Folder 25)
  - Minimum Wage, 1979 (Box 13, Folder 26)
  - Minimum Wage: Wells Plaza Corp. et al., 1958-1960 (Box 13, Folder 27)
  - "Minorities": Protest, 1977-1979 (Box 13, Folder 28)
  - Montalvo, Manuel, undated (Box 13, Folder 29)
  - National Labor Relations Board: Correspondence, 1981-1983 (Box 13, Folder 30)
  - National Negro Congress, 1946 (Box 13, Folder 31)
  - Nedick's, 1937 (Box 13, Folder 32)
  - Negotiations: General, 1970-1980 (Box 13, Folder 33)
  - Negro Hotel Workers Council, undated (Box 13, Folder 34)
  - Neighborhood Service Councils, 1967 (Box 13, Folder 35)
  - New Jersey Organizing, 1977 (Box 13, Folder 36)
  - New Year's Eve, 1984 (Box 13, Folder 37)
  - New York Athletic Club: Potter Case, 1950-1951 (Box 13, Folder 38)
  - NYC Central Labor Council, 1980-1983 (Box 13, Folder 39)
  - New York Labor War Chest, undated (Box 13, Folder 40)
  - New York State AFL-CIO, 1981-1982 (Box 13, Folder 41)
  - New York State Council of HERE, 1963-1982 (Box 13, Folder 42)
  - Nightwork: New York State Department of Labor Report, 1949 (Box 13, Folder 43)
  - Norrie, E.W., Estate of, 1938-1939 (Box 13, Folder 44)
  - Obermeier Defense Committee: Addresses, 1947 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Obermeier Defense Committee: Bank Statements, Nov 1947-Aug 1948 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Obermeier Defense Committee: Bank Statements, Sep 1948-Dec 1951 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Obermeier Defense Committee: Brief on Behalf of Michael J. Obermeier, 1949 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Obermeier Defense Committee: Checkbook and Register, 1947-1950 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Obermeier Defense Committee: Clippings, 1947-1949 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Obermeier Defense Committee: Collection Lists, 1947 (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Obermeier Defense Committee: Collection Lists, 1948 (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Obermeier Defense Committee: Collection Lists from Receipt Book (I), undated (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - Obermeier Defense Committee: Collection Lists from Receipt Book (II), undated (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - Obermeier Defense Committee: Collection Lists from Receipt Book (III), undated (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - Obermeier Defense Committee: Collection Lists from Receipt Book (IV), undated (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - Obermeier Defense Committee: Collection Lists from Receipt Book (V), undated (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - Obermeier Defense Committee: Collection Lists from Receipt Book (VI), undated (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - Obermeier Defense Committee: Collection Lists from Receipt Book (VII), undated (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - Obermeier Defense Committee: Collection Lists from Receipt Book (VIII), undated (Box 14, Folder 16)
  - Obermeier Defense Committee: Collection Lists from Receipt Book (IX), undated (Box 14, Folder 17)
  - Obermeier Defense Committee: Collection Lists from Receipt Book (X), undated (Box 14, Folder 18)
  - Obermeier Defense Committee: Collection Lists from Receipt Book (XI), undated (Box 14, Folder 19)
  - Obermeier Defense Committee: Collection Lists from Receipt Book (XII), undated (Box 14, Folder 20)
  - Obermeier Defense Committee: Correspondence, 1947 (Box 14, Folder 21)
  - Obermeier Defense Committee: Correspondence, 1948 (Box 14, Folder 22)
  - Obermeier Defense Committee: Donation Collection Books (I), 1947-1948 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Obermeier Defense Committee: Donation Collection Books (II), 1947-1948 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Obermeier Defense Committee: Donation Collection Books (III), 1947-1948 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Obermeier Defense Committee: Election Campaign Collection List Register, 1954 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Obermeier Defense Committee: Election Conference Meetings, 1954-1955 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Obermeier Defense Committee: Elections, Financial Statement, Campaign Fund, 1954 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Obermeier Defense Committee: Paid Invoices, 1947-1951 (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Obermeier Defense Committee: Pamphlets, 1947-1949 (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Obermeier Defense Committee: Press Releases, American Committee for Protection of the Foreign Born, 1946-1950 (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Obermeier Defense Committee: Receipt Books Out, 1947-1948 (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - Obermeier Defense Committee: Receipts, 1947-1950 (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - Obermeier Defense Committee: "The Lamp", 1947-1949 (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - Obermeier, Michael J., 1947-1951 (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - Occupational Opportunities Survey: Food Trades, undated; 1963 (Box 15, Folder 14)
  - Office and Professional Employees International Union (OPEIU): Local 6 Staff Union, 1950-1976 (Box 15, Folder 15)
  - OPEIU: Local 153, 1955-1980 (Box 15, Folder 16)
  - Officer of the Day, 1983 (Box 15, Folder 17)
  - Old-Timers Club, 1947-1948 (Box 15, Folder 18)
  - Opposition, 1947 (Box 15, Folder 19)
  - Opposition, 1948 (Box 15, Folder 20)
  - Opposition: Elias Simadiris Suit (Waldorf-Astoria), 1952; 1976-1978 (Box 15, Folder 21)
  - Organizer's Guide, undated (Box 15, Folder 22)
  - Organizer's Report to 5th Assembly, 1961 (Box 15, Folder 23)
  - Organizing, undated (Box 15, Folder 24)
  - Organizing, 1980 (Box 15, Folder 25)
  - Organizing: Leaflets, Restaurants, 1930s (Box 15, Folder 26)
  - Organizing: Leaflets, 1940s-1970s (Box 15, Folder 27)
  - Organizing: Literature, undated (Box 15, Folder 28)
  - Pamphlets, undated (Box 15, Folder 29)
  - Paulista, Lubos, undated (Box 15, Folder 30)
  - Payroll Ledger: Business Agents and Organizers, 1943-1944 (Box 15, Folder 31)
  - Pension and Welfare Fund: Correspondence, 1968-1972 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Pension and Welfare Fund: Trustees Meeting, Dec 1976 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Pension and Welfare Fund: Trustees Meeting, Feb 3 1977 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Pension and Welfare Fund: Trustees Meeting, Feb 4 1977 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Pension and Welfare Fund: Trustees Meeting, Mar 1977 (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Pension and Welfare Fund: Trustees Meeting, Apr 1977 (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Pension and Welfare Fund: Trustees Meeting, Jun 14 1977 (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Pension and Welfare Fund: Trustees Meeting, Jun 29 1977 (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - Pension and Welfare Fund: Trustees Meeting, Jul 1977 (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - Pension and Welfare Fund: Trustees Meeting, Oct 1977 (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - Pension and Welfare Fund: Trustees Meeting, Dec 1977 (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - Pension Fund, 1980 (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - Pension Fund, 1981 (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - Pension Fund, 1985 (Box 16, Folder 14)
  - Pension Fund: Chicago, 1975-1977 (Box 16, Folder 15)
  - Pension Fund: International, 1975 (Box 16, Folder 16)
  - Pension Fund: Local 60, 1977 (Box 16, Folder 17)
  - Pension Fund: Local 71, 1976 (Box 16, Folder 18)
  - Pension Fund: Local 115, 1976-1977 (Box 16, Folder 19)
  - Pension Fund: Merger Local 1 and 89, Cafeteria Industry, 1982-1983 (Box 16, Folder 20)
  - Pension Trust Fund, 1969-1977 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Petitions from Members, 1981-1982 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Picket Schedules, 1980-1983 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Piping Rock Restaurant, 1937 (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Pitta, Vito, 1980 (Box 17, Folder 4a)
  - Political Action Committee, 1982 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Political Activity, undated; 1979-1983 (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Political Materials, 1930s-1940s (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - Puerto Rican Hurricane Relief, 1975 (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - Puerto Rican Minimum Wage Industry Committee No.78, 1968 (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - Puerto Rican Workers, 1948-1964 (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - Puerto Rico: Hotels, 1984 (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - Puffing Billy Restaurant, 1979-1980 (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - Queens Community Labor Committee, Jun-05 (Box 17, Folder 13)
  - Racketeering (Locals 16 and 302), 1933-1937 (Box 17, Folder 14)
  - Rank and File Groups, undated (Box 17, Folder 15)
  - Recognition Agreement, 1982 (Box 17, Folder 17)
  - Reinstatement of Members, undated (Box 17, Folder 18)
  - Report by Local 6 Administration, May-05 (Box 17, Folder 19)
  - Representatives: Lists, May-05 (Box 17, Folder 20)
  - Retirement Plan, 1964-1978 (Box 17, Folder 21)
  - Riker Restaurant Associates, 1937 (Box 17, Folder 22)
  - Rodriguez, Eva I. (Secretary-Treasurer), Dec 1985-May 1986 (Box 17, Folder 23)
  - Rodriguez, Eva I. (Secretary-Treasurer), Jun-Nov 1986 (Box 17, Folder 24)
  - Roth, Rochelle, 1982 (Box 17, Folder 25)
  - Rubin, Jay (President): Certificates (honors, appointments), 1963-1973 (Box 17, Folder 26)
  - Rubin, Jay (President): Certificates (honors, appointments) (Oversize), 1963-1977, undated (Box Tamiment Shared MSOS005, Folder 1)
  - Rubin, Jay (President): Convention Materials (Local 6, 12th), 1968 (Box 17, Folder 27)
  - Rubin, Jay (President): Correspondence, Victor Medina, 1965 (Box 17, Folder 28)
  - Rubin, Jay (President): Local 6 Election and Objections Committee, 1968 (Box 17, Folder 29)
  - Rubin, Jay (President): Reports, 1976-1978 (Box 17, Folder 30)
  - Sandi's Restaurant, 1982 (Box 17, Folder 31)
  - Save the Union Committee, 1951 (Box 17, Folder 31)
  - Scholarship: Correspondence, 1954 (Box 17, Folder 32)
  - Scholarship: Correspondence, 1961 (Box 17, Folder 33)
  - Scholarship: Correspondence, 1963-1964 (Box 17, Folder 34)
  - Scholarship: Correspondence, 1965-1966 (Box 17, Folder 35)
  - Scholarship: Correspondence, 1967-1968 (Box 17, Folder 36)
  - Scholarships: Lane Memorial Fund, 1962 (Box 17, Folder 38)
  - Schrafft's, 1937-1939 (Box 17, Folder 39)
  - Segal, Martin, 1947-1948 (Box 17, Folder 40)
  - Segal, Martin, 1985 (Box 17, Folder 41)
  - Seamen's Church Institute, 1975 (Box 17, Folder 42)
  - Seamen's Church Institute, 1984 (Box 17, Folder 43)
  - Shop Chairmen, undated (Box 17, Folder 44)
  - Shea and Gould, 1980-1987 (Box 17, Folder 45)
  - Sirch, Richard, undated (Box 17, Folder 46)
  - Southern Christian Leadership Conference (SCLC), undated (Box 17, Folder 47)
  - South Gate Towers, 1978 (Box 17, Folder 48)
  - Spanish-American Workers Action Committee, See Comite de Accion de Trabajdores Hispano-Americanos (CATHA) Box 6, Folder 15, 1977-1980 (Box 17)
  - Staff, 1978-1981 (Box 17, Folder 49)
  - Staff, 1982 (Box 17, Folder 50)
  - Staff Assignments, 1979 (Box 17, Folder 51)
  - Staff Meetings, 1984 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Staff Pension Plan, 1977 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Staff Pension Trust, 1965-1968 (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Strike Committees, undated (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Strike-Related Discharges, 1985 (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Tavern on the Green: Picket Line, 1985 (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Testimonial Luncheons, 1970-1975 (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - Tips, 1942-1982 (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - Traveling Cards, 1953-1954 (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - Traveling Cards, 1970-1981 (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - Trusteeship, 1951 (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - "Twenty-Five Candles": Script, 1964 (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - "Twenty-Five Candles": Speeches, 1964 (Box 18, Folder 13)
  - Unemployment Compensation, 1982 (Box 18, Folder 14)
  - United Progressive Group, 1940 (Box 18, Folder 15)
  - United Socialist Workers Coalition, undated (Box 18, Folder 16)
  - Wages: Comparative, 1973-1977 (Box 18, Folder 17)
  - Waiters: Shifts, 1982 (Box 18, Folder 18)
  - Welfare Fund: International, 1975-1976 (Box 18, Folder 19)
  - Welfare Trust: Chicago, 1975 (Box 18, Folder 20)
  - Whelan Drug Co., 1936 (Box 18, Folder 21)
  - Wirtz vs. Local 6, 1966-1967 (Box 18, Folder 22)
  - Wood, Mabel Travis: "Our Stalinist Hotel Unions", 1950 (Box 18, Folder 23)
  - YMCA, 1982 (Box 18, Folder 24)
  - Series IV: Hotels
    - Abbey, 1949-1950 (Box 21, Folder 1)
    - Ambassador, 1948-1955 (Box 21, Folder 2)
    - Ambassador: Minutes, 1954-1959 (Box 22, Folder 3)
    - Ansonia, 1950-1952 (Box 21, Folder 4)
    - Astor (Sheraton Astor), 1950-1961 (Box 21, Folder 5)
    - Astor (Sheraton Astor): Minutes, 1952-1961 (Box 21, Folder 6)
    - Barrings, 1959-1961 (Box 21, Folder 7)
    - Beacon, 1950 (Box 21, Folder 8)
    - Belvedere, 1948-1950 (Box 21, Folder 9)
    - Belmont Plaza, 1948-1958 (Box 21, Folder 10)
    - Belmont Plaza: Minutes, 1951-1958 (Box 21, Folder 11)
    - Biltmore, 1948-1960 (Box 21, Folder 12)
    - Biltmore: Minutes, 1950-1959 (Box 21, Folder 12a)
    - Bossert, 1948-1949 (Box 21, Folder 13)
    - Brevoort, 1948-1951 (Box 21, Folder 14)
    - Chatham, 1951 (Box 21, Folder 15)
    - Commodore, 1952-1961 (Box 21, Folder 16)
    - Concourse Plaza, 1946-1959 (Box 21, Folder 17)
    - Cornish Arms, 1950-1951 (Box 21, Folder 18)
    - Croydon, 1949-1959 (Box 21, Folder 19)
    - Delmonico's, 1948-1959 (Box 21, Folder 20)
    - Dorset, 1952 (Box 21, Folder 21)
    - Edison, 1948-1960 (Box 21, Folder 22)
    - Empire, 1948-1950 (Box 21, Folder 23)
    - Esplanade, 1948-1960 (Box 21, Folder 24)
    - Essex House, 1947-1959 (Box 21, Folder 25)
    - Etna Restaurant, 1951 (Box 21, Folder 26)
    - Fifth Avenue, 1950-1951 (Box 21, Folder 27)
    - Franklin, 1948 (Box 21, Folder 28)
    - George Washington, 1948-1957 (Box 21, Folder 29)
    - Gotham, 1948-1958 (Box 21, Folder 30)
    - Governor Clinton, 1950-1953 (Box 21, Folder 31)
    - Gramercy Park, 1948-1959 (Box 21, Folder 32)
    - Granada, 1948-1960 (Box 21, Folder 33)
    - Great Northern, 1948-1955 (Box 21, Folder 34)